maximus.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | MAXIMUS

Effective February 16, 2017

## Our Commitment to Privacy

MAXIMUS, Inc. (together with its affiliates, "MAXIMUS") respects your privacy and we have developed the following policy to demonstrate our commitment to you. This privacy policy applies to personal information we collect about you on the MAXIMUS website located at [www.maximus.com](http://www.maximus.com/) (the “Site”) and describes the types of information collected, how that information is used, and the choices users have about collection and use of this information. This privacy policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities, websites other than this Site, or products and services not available or enabled via this Site, except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Information We Collect

Although much of the Site is available without registration or providing personal information, in order to take advantage of some of our Site’s features, you will be asked to provide personal information. This personal information is provided voluntarily by you, the user, in order to participate or register for a particular product or service, or when you otherwise communicate with us or the Site. Personal information will be collected at various pages on the Site, including when you:

  * Submit an online inquiry
  * Submit an investor relations information request
  * Sign up for email alerts, newsletters and other MAXIMUS information
  * Submit an employment application

We clearly identify data you must provide so we can deliver the services or information you request. MAXIMUS may ask that you provide personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP/Postal code), country of residence, email address, employer, job title and department, telephone numbers and other personal information. Providing this information is optional, but failure to do so in some cases will limit the services available to you.

In addition, our web servers automatically collect and log web usage data from you when you visit the Site. This information, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, referring sites, pages viewed, browser type, operating system, CPU speed, referring or exit web pages, and length of visit, informs us about how visitors use and navigate the Site.

## How We Use and Share the Information Collected

MAXIMUS does not share your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties, but we may use your information to, among other things:

  * Provide newsletters and information about MAXIMUS
  * Provide the information or service requested or otherwise respond to your inquiries
  * Improve the content, navigation and efficiency of the Site
  * Make you aware of other benefits, products, services or events offered by MAXIMUS that may interest you
  * Enforce the MAXIMUS Terms of Use and otherwise prevent illegal or improper activity related to the Site

In order to respond to an information request you submit through the Site, we may share your personal information with our affiliated companies that may be able to respond directly to your inquiry. In addition, we may disclose your information to third parties (1) in connection with a merger, sale or consolidation of all or substantially all our assets, or (2) to comply with valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order. By using this Site, you agree and acknowledge that personal information collected through the Site may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any country around the world, including the United States.

We may use and share with others aggregated or anonymous (not personally identifiable) information that we have collected based on web usage data, surveys or statistical information that we have compiled about our users.

## Employment Applications

MAXIMUS collects your personal information to allow us to process your application for employment. Your personal information will be treated as confidential and made accessible only to authorized MAXIMUS employees and/or suppliers, external representatives and third parties engaged specifically to support MAXIMUS in conducting recruitment and selection or onboarding activities and for employment purposes in respect of successful candidates. 

You may be asked to provide additional information not contained in your application to assist the recruitment and selection processes (for example, references or for vetting and/or security checks). If you choose not to provide the requested information, it may limit our ability to assess your suitability for employment and we may be unable to proceed with your application. 

MAXIMUS contracts with iCIMS, a third party provider of talent acquisition services. When accessing MAXIMUS Careers/Job Opportunities, the iCIMS Privacy Policy and Terms of Use shall also apply. You can access the iCIMS Privacy Policy at <https://www.icims.com/legal/privacy-policy-website> and the Terms of Use at <https://www.icims.com/legal/terms-of-use>.

## Cookies

Like most websites, we employ "cookies," "web beacons," and similar devices to help you more efficiently use the Site and to track your activities. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables MAXIMUS to record your activities and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Cookies from MAXIMUS can only be read by MAXIMUS websites. A web beacon is a small transparent gif image that is embedded in an HTML page or email used to track when the page or email has been viewed. MAXIMUS uses cookies and similar devices to track your use of the Site, types of Products and Services viewed and information downloaded, count visitors we receive daily, and our web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer. MAXIMUS does not generally use this information to identify you personally. If you do not want your browser to accept cookies, you can modify the cookie option in your browser’s settings. However, some Site features or services may not function properly or be accessible without cookies.

## Choice

Certain email alerts you sign up for on the Site (e.g., investor email notifications) allow you to update your notification preferences online. You may also change your preferences regarding the types of communications you receive from MAXIMUS by emailing us at [PrivacyOfficial@maximus.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficial@maximus.com).

## California Residents

If you are a California resident, California law (Calif. Bus. & Prof. Code § 22575-22578) entitles you to request information concerning whether your personal information has been disclosed to nonaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with nonaffiliated third parties for such purposes.

"Do Not Track" is a preference you can set in your web browser to let the websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting information about you. The Site does not currently respond to a "Do Not Track" or similar signals.

## Security

MAXIMUS uses various technological and procedural security measures in order to protect the personal information we collect through the Site from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. **We have documented Information Security & Privacy policies to address data protection** **.** We **regularly** provide information security and privacy awareness training to our employees. However, you should be aware that, due to the open and unsecured character of the internet, MAXIMUS cannot be responsible for the security of transmissions of personal information over the internet. **We  have prepared a formal incident response plan in case of a data breach.** Please do not submit Protected Health Information through our Site. Please contact the individual program with any questions or enrollment requests

## Children

The Site is not directed toward children under 13 years of age, nor do we knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

## Links

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Links do not imply endorsement by MAXIMUS. Please be aware that these other sites are not subject to the MAXIMUS privacy policy and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policies of those sites when you visit them.

## Reviewing and Correcting Your Information

We try to keep information about you accurate and current. Certain services available on the Site allow you to receive investor email notifications. If you receive such notifications, you may cancel their receipt at any time by clicking a link on the bottom of the email. Personal information submitted through this Site may be updated by visiting the location in which you submitted it. To update or correct such information and privacy preferences, you may write MAXIMUS at the address below. In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site or otherwise where you provided your personal information.

Personal information maintained by any of our contracts administered on behalf of federal, state or local government entities should be corrected by contracting the customer service department in the individual program.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy policy. Please check the Site from time to time for the most current version of our privacy policy. Your continued use of the Site after we have notified you of changes as described above constitutes your acceptance of the changes.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us by:

Email:  

Mail:  
MAXIMUS Privacy Office  
1891 Metro Center Drive  
Reston, VA 20190 USA
